A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV.The Wartime Papers of Robert E. Lee, 1959-1961 (photostats and card index: 1832-1870)., Extent: 21 cu. ft. (Box 85-149.)
  - Transcripts, 1833-1865.
    - Chapter Three.
      - To Wife, 1861 November 5. (Box 94, Folder 56)
      - Special Orders, Number 206, 1861 November 5. (Box 94, Folder 57)
      - General Orders, Number 1, 1861 November 8. (Box 94, Folder 58)
      - To Secretary of War, 1861 November 9. (Box 94, Folder 59)
      - To "My Precious Daughter," 1861 November 15. (Box 94, Folder 60)
      - To Wife, 1861 November 18. (Box 94, Folder 61)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1861 November 21. (Box 94, Folder 62)
      - To Annie and Agnes, 1861 November 22. (Box 94, Folder 63)
      - To Wife, 1861 December 12. (Box 94, Folder 64)
      - To Messers. W. Elliott, E. Rhett, and L. Youmanis, 1861 December 3. (Box 94, Folder 65)
      - To Annie, 1861 December 9. (Box 94, Folder 66)
      - To General S.R. Gist, 1861 December 16. (Box 94, Folder 67)
      - To Secretary of War, 1861 December 20. (Box 94, Folder 68)
      - To A. Magrath, 1861 December 24. (Box 94, Folder 69)
      - To Wife, 1861 December 25. (Box 94, Folder 70)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1861 December 29. (Box 94, Folder 71)
      - To Governor F.W. Pickens, 1862 January 2. (Box 94, Folder 72)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1862 January 4. (Box 94, Folder 73)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 January 8. (Box 94, Folder 74)
      - To Honorable C. Furman, 1862 January 17. (Box 94, Folder 75)
      - To Wife, 1862 January 18. (Box 94, Folder 76)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1862 January 19. (Box 94, Folder 77)
      - To Wife, 1862 January 28. (Box 94, Folder 78)
      - To General J. Anderson, 1862 January 28. (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - To General T. Drayton, 1862 February 4. (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 February 6. (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - To Wife, 1862 February 8. (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 February 10. (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - To Governor Brown, 1862 February 10. (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - To General N. Evans, 1862 February 15. (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - To General H. Wayne, 1862 February 15. (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 February 18. (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - To General R. Ripley, 1862 February 19. (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - To General J. Trapier, 1862 February 19. (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - To Governor Brown, 1862 February 22. (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - To Wife, 1862 February 23. (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - To Governor Milton, 1862 February 24. (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - To General J. Trapier, 1862 March 1. (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - To Annie, 1862 March 2. (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 March 2. (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Chapter Four.
      - General Orders, Number 14, 1862 March 13. (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - To Wife, 1862 March 14. (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - To Wife, 1862 March 15. (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - To General T. Holmes, 1862 March 16. (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 March 17. (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 March 18. (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - To General E. Johnson, 1862 March 21. (Box 95, Folder 24)
      - To Wife, 1862 March 22. (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - To General J.E. Johnston, 1862 March 25. (Box 95, Folder 26)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 March 25. (Box 95, Folder 27)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 March 26. (Box 95, Folder 28)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 March 28. (Box 95, Folder 29)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 March 28. (Box 95, Folder 30)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 March 29. (Box 95, Folder 31)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 March 31. (Box 95, Folder 32)
      - To General T. Holmes, 1862 April 1. (Box 95, Folder 33)
      - To Wife, 1862 April 4. (Box 95, Folder 34)
      - To S.R. Mallory, 1862 April 8. (Box 95, Folder 35)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 April 9. (Box 95, Folder 36)
      - To General Pemberton, 1862 April 10. (Box 95, Folder 37)
      - Special Order, Number 6, 1862 April 12. (Box 95, Folder 38)
      - To R.S. Ewell, 1862 April 17. (Box 95, Folder 39)
      - To General H. Heth, 1862 April 18. (Box 95, Folder 40)
      - To General H. Marshall, 1862 April 18. (Box 95, Folder 41)
      - To General E. Johnson, 1862 April 18. (Box 95, Folder 42)
      - To General C. Field, 1862 April 19. (Box 95, Folder 43)
      - To General C. Field, 1862 April 19. (Box 95, Folder 44)
      - To General Pemberton, 1862 April 20. (Box 95, Folder 45)
      - To General C. Field, 1862 April 21. (Box 95, Folder 46)
      - To General T. J. Jackson, 1862 April 21. (Box 95, Folder 47)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 April 21. (Box 95, Folder 48)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 April 21. (Box 95, Folder 49)
      - To Wife, 1862 April 22. (Box 95, Folder 50)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 April 23. (Box 95, Folder 51)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 April 25. (Box 95, Folder 52)
      - To T.J. Jackson, 1862 April 25. (Box 95, Folder 53)
      - To General J. Anderson, 1862 April 25. (Box 95, Folder 54)
      - To Agnes, 1862 April 26. (Box 95, Folder 55)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 April 27. (Box 95, Folder 56)
      - To General T. Holmes, 1862 April 28. (Box 95, Folder 57)
      - To T.J. Jackson, 1862 April 29. (Box 95, Folder 58)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 April 30. (Box 95, Folder 59)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 April 30. (Box 95, Folder 60)
      - To T.J. Jackson, 1862 May 1. (Box 95, Folder 61)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 May 1. (Box 95, Folder 62)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 2. (Box 95, Folder 63)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 May 6. (Box 95, Folder 64)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 May 8. (Box 95, Folder 65)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 8. (Box 95, Folder 66)
      - To General R. Ewell, 1862 May 8. (Box 95, Folder 67)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 May 8. (Box 95, Folder 68)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 10. (Box 95, Folder 69)
      - To General J. Anderson, 1862 May 11. (Box 95, Folder 70)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 11. (Box 95, Folder 71)
      - To Wife, 1862 May 13. (Box 95, Folder 72)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 15. (Box 95, Folder 73)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 May 16. (Box 95, Folder 74)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 May 16. (Box 95, Folder 75)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 17. (Box 95, Folder 76)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 18. (Box 95, Folder 77)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 21. (Box 95, Folder 78)
      - To J.E. Johnston, 1862 May 22. (Box 95, Folder 79)
    - Chapter Five.
      - Special Order, Number 22, 1862 June 1. (Box 95, Folder 80)
      - To Major W. Stevens, 1862 June 3. (Box 95, Folder 81)
      - To Major W. Stevens, 1862 June 4. (Box 95, Folder 82)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 5. (Box 95, Folder 83)
      - To Colonel J. Gorgas, 1862 June 5. (Box 95, Folder 84)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 June 5. (Box 95, Folder 85)
      - Taylor to Magruder, 1862 June 5. (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 June 8. (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - To General R. Ransom, 1862 June 8. (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 June 9. (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 10. (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - To Colonel A. Myers, 1862 June 10. (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - To Wife, 1862 June 10. (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - To Wife, 1862 June 10. (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 June 11. (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - To General A.P. Hill, 1862 June 11. (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 June 11. (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 13. (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 June 16. (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - To General T.H. Holmes, 1862 June 18. (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - To General T.H. Holmes, 1862 June 21. (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - To S.R. Mallory, 1862 June 21. (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - To Mrs. W.H.F. Lee, 1862 June 22. (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - General Order, Number 74, 1862 June 23. (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - General Orders, Number 75, 1862 June 24. (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 24. (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - To Wife, 1862 June 25. (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 26. (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 June 26. (Box 96, Folder 23)
      - Chilton to Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 26. (Box 96, Folder 24)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 27. (Box 96, Folder 25)
      - To General B. Huger, 1862 June 27. (Box 96, Folder 26)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 June 28. (Box 96, Folder 27)
      - To General J.B. Magruder, 1862 June 28. (Box 96, Folder 28)
      - Chilton to Magruder, 1862 June 28. (Box 96, Folder 29)
      - To General Magruder, 1862 June 29. (Box 96, Folder 30)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 June 29. (Box 96, Folder 31)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 2. (Box 96, Folder 32)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 3. (Box 96, Folder 33)
      - To Major General Hill, 1862 July 4. (Box 96, Folder 34)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 4. (Box 96, Folder 35)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 6. (Box 96, Folder 36)
      - General Order, Number 75, 1862 July 7. (Box 96, Folder 37)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 March 6. (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - Chapter Six.
      - To Jefferson Davis 1862 July 9. (Box 96, Folder 39)
      - To Wife, 1862 July 9. (Box 96, Folder 40)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 July 11. (Box 96, Folder 41)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 July 12. (Box 96, Folder 42)
      - To Fitzhugh, 1862 July 15. (Box 96, Folder 43)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 18. (Box 96, Folder 44)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1862 July 18. (Box 96, Folder 45)
      - To Major General George B. McClellan, 1862 July 21. (Box 96, Folder 46)
      - To General Longstreet, 1862 July 23. (Box 96, Folder 47)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 July 23. (Box 96, Folder 48)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 July 25. (Box 96, Folder 49)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 25. (Box 96, Folder 50)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 25. (Box 96, Folder 51)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 July 26. (Box 96, Folder 52)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 July 26. (Box 96, Folder 53)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 July 27. (Box 96, Folder 54)
      - To Miss M.C. Lee, 1862 July 28. (Box 96, Folder 55)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 July 28. (Box 96, Folder 56)
      - To S.S. Lee, 1862 July 31. (Box 96, Folder 57)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1862 August 2. (Box 96, Folder 58)
      - To Wife, 1862 August 3. (Box 96, Folder 59)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1862 August 3. (Box 96, Folder 60)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1862 August 4. (Box 96, Folder 61)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 August 4. (Box 96, Folder 62)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1862 August 7. (Box 96, Folder 63)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 7. (Box 96, Folder 64)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 August 7. (Box 96, Folder 65)
      - To Governor H.T. Clark, 1862 August 8. (Box 96, Folder 66)
      - To Annie and Agnes, 1862 August 9. (Box 96, Folder 67)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 August 12. (Box 96, Folder 68)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1862 August 13. (Box 96, Folder 69)
      - To Secretary of War, 1862 August 14. (Box 96, Folder 70)
      - To General Longstreet, 1862 August 14. (Box 96, Folder 71)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 14. (Box 96, Folder 72)
      - To General G.W. Smith, 1862 August 14. (Box 96, Folder 73)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1862 August 14. (Box 96, Folder 74)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 15. (Box 96, Folder 75)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 16. (Box 96, Folder 76)
      - To Wife, 1862 August 17. (Box 96, Folder 77)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 17. (Box 96, Folder 78)
      - Special Orders, Number (?), 1862 August 19. (Box 96, Folder 79)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1862 August 19. (Box 96, Folder 80)
      - To G.W. Randolph, 1862 August 19. (Box 96, Folder 81)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 21. (Box 96, Folder 82)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 23. (Box 96, Folder 83)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 24. (Box 96, Folder 84)
      - To Wife, 1862 August 25. (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - To Colonel J.F. Gilmer, 1862 August 25. (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 27. (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 29. (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 30. (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 August 30. (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 August 30. (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 3. (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 18. (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 June 8. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Chapter Seven.
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 3. (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 4. (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 5. (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 6. (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - To General G.W. Smith, 1862 September 7. (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 7. (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - To "The People of Maryland," 1862 September 8. (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 8. (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 8. (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Special Orders, Number 191, 1862 September 9. (Box 97, Folder 20)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 9. (Box 97, Folder 21)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 9. (Box 97, Folder 22)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 12. (Box 97, Folder 23)
      - Long to General L. McLaws, 1862 September 13. (Box 97, Folder 24)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 13. (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Chilton to General McLaws, 1862 September 14. (Box 97, Folder 26)
      - To Major General L. McLaws, 1862 September 14. (Box 97, Folder 27)
      - Long to General McLaws, 1862 September 15. (Box 97, Folder 28)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 16. (Box 97, Folder 29)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 September 18. (Box 97, Folder 30)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 August 19. (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Chapter Eight.
      - To Honorable G.W. Randolph, 1862 November 7. (Box 97, Folder 32)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1862 November 7. (Box 97, Folder 33)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 9. (Box 97, Folder 34)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1862 November 9. (Box 97, Folder 35)
      - To Honorable G.W. Randolph, 1862 November 10. (Box 97, Folder 36)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1862 November 10. (Box 97, Folder 37)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 12. (Box 97, Folder 38)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 14. (Box 97, Folder 39)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 14. (Box 97, Folder 40)
      - To General W.H.F. Lee, 1862 November 15. (Box 97, Folder 41)
      - To Honorable G.W. Randolph, 1862 November 17. (Box 97, Folder 42)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 November 17. (Box 97, Folder 43)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 November 18. (Box 97, Folder 44)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 19. (Box 97, Folder 45)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 November 20. (Box 97, Folder 46)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 November 22. (Box 97, Folder 47)
      - To Wife, 1862 November 22. (Box 97, Folder 48)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 23. (Box 97, Folder 49)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 November 25. (Box 97, Folder 50)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 25. (Box 97, Folder 51)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 27. (Box 97, Folder 52)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 November 27. (Box 97, Folder 53)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 November 28. (Box 97, Folder 54)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1862 November 28. (Box 97, Folder 55)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1862 December 2. (Box 97, Folder 56)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 December 6. (Box 97, Folder 57)
      - To Wife, 1862 December 7. (Box 97, Folder 58)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1862 December 8. (Box 97, Folder 59)
      - To Mrs. W.H.F. Lee, 1862 December 10. (Box 97, Folder 60)
      - To Wife, 1862 December 11. (Box 97, Folder 61)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 11. (Box 97, Folder 62)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 December 11. (Box 97, Folder 63)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 December 12. (Box 97, Folder 64)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 13. (Box 97, Folder 65)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 December 13. (Box 97, Folder 66)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1862 December 13. (Box 97, Folder 67)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 14. (Box 97, Folder 68)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 14. (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 15. (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 16. (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 10. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Nine.
      - To Wife, 1862 December 16. (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 16. (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1862 December 16. (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - To General G.W. Smith, 1863 January 4. (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 January 5. (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 January 5. (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 January 6. (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 January 9. (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 January 10. (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 January 13. (Box 98, Folder 14)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 January 19. (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 January 20. (Box 98, Folder 16)
      - To Colonel J. Gorgas, 1863 January 22. (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 January 23. (Box 98, Folder 18)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 January 26. (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - To Wife, 1863 January 29. (Box 98, Folder 20)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 January 29. (Box 98, Folder 21)
      - To Honorable J.A. Seddon, 1863 February 4. (Box 98, Folder 22)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 February 5. (Box 98, Folder 23)
      - To Agnes, 1863 February 6. (Box 98, Folder 24)
      - To Wife, 1863 February 8. (Box 98, Folder 25)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 February 13. (Box 98, Folder 26)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 February 15. (Box 98, Folder 27)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 February 16. (Box 98, Folder 28)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 February 18. (Box 98, Folder 29)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 February 18. (Box 98, Folder 30)
      - To Agnes, 1863 February 20. (Box 98, Folder 31)
      - To Wife, 1863 February 23. (Box 98, Folder 32)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 February 26. (Box 98, Folder 33)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 February 28. (Box 98, Folder 34)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 March 3. (Box 98, Folder 35)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 March 6. (Box 98, Folder 36)
      - To Wife, 1863 March 9. (Box 98, Folder 37)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 March 19. (Box 98, Folder 38)
      - To Wife, 1863 March 19. (Box 98, Folder 39)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 March 21. (Box 98, Folder 40)
      - To Wife, 1863 March 21. (Box 98, Folder 41)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 March 27. (Box 98, Folder 42)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 March 27. (Box 98, Folder 43)
      - To Wife, 1863 March 27. (Box 98, Folder 44)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 March 30. (Box 98, Folder 45)
    - Chapter Ten.
      - To Wife, 1863 April 3. (Box 98, Folder 46)
      - To General Arnold Elzey, 1863 April 6. (Box 98, Folder 47)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 April 9. (Box 98, Folder 48)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 10. (Box 98, Folder 49)
      - To Agnes, 1863 April 11. (Box 98, Folder 50)
      - To Wife, 1863 April 12. (Box 98, Folder 51)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 16. (Box 98, Folder 52)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 April 16. (Box 98, Folder 53)
      - To Lt. General Longstreet, 1863 April 17. (Box 98, Folder 54)
      - To General W.E. Jones, 1863 April 18. (Box 98, Folder 55)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 18. (Box 98, Folder 56)
      - To Wife, 1863 April 19. (Box 98, Folder 57)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1863 April 23. (Box 98, Folder 58)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 April 23. (Box 98, Folder 59)
      - To Wife, 1863 April 24. (Box 98, Folder 60)
      - To General J. Longstreet, 1863 April 27. (Box 98, Folder 61)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 62)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 63)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 64)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 65)
      - Marshall to Colonel Critcher, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 66)
      - To General L. McLaws, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 67)
      - To General R.H. Anderson, 1863 April 29. (Box 98, Folder 68)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 69)
      - To General R.H. Anderson, 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 70)
      - Special Orders, 121, 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 71)
      - To General L. McLaws, 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 72)
      - To T.J. Jackson, 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 73)
      - To (?), 1863 April 30. (Box 98, Folder 74)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 May 1. (Box 98, Folder 75)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 2. (Box 98, Folder 76)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - To General J.E.B. Stuart, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - To General T.J. Jackson, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - To General J.A. Early, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - To General L. McLaws, 1863 May 3. (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - To General L. McLaws, 1863 May 4. (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 5. (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 6. (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 6. (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 7. (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 7. (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - To General James Longstreet, 1863 May 7. (Box 99, Folder 14)
      - To General S. Cooper, 1863 September 21-23. (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Chapter Eleven.
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 10. (Box 99, Folder 16)
      - To Honorable James A. Seddon, 1863 May 10. (Box 99, Folder 17)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 11. (Box 99, Folder 18)
      - To G.W.C. Lee, 1863 May 11. (Box 99, Folder 19)
      - General Order, Number 61, 1863 May 11. (Box 99, Folder 20)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1863 May 16. (Box 99, Folder 21)
      - To General Isaac R. Trimble, 1863 May 20. (Box 99, Folder 22)
      - To Wife, 1863 May 20. (Box 99, Folder 23)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 20. (Box 99, Folder 24)
      - To Honorable J. A. Seddon, 1863 May 20. (Box 99, Folder 25)
      - To General J.B. Hood, 1863 May 21. (Box 99, Folder 26)
      - To Wife, 1863 May 23. (Box 99, Folder 27)
      - To Agnes, 1863 May 25. (Box 99, Folder 28)
      - To General D.H. Hill, 1863 May 25. (Box 99, Folder 29)
      - To General Arnold Elzey, 1863 May 27. (Box 99, Folder 30)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 29. (Box 99, Folder 31)
      - To Jefferson Davis, 1863 May 30. (Box 99, Folder 32)